Previously on... Desperate housewives
前情提要
sounds to me as if someone'slet go of his rage.
看起来某人丢弃了自己的愤怒
- Maybe I have.
- 可能我是的
Well,i haven'T.
但是我没有
Felicia took matters into her own hands.
Felicia要自己解决问题
You want me to call offthe wedding,I'll do it.
只要你想让我取消婚礼，我就会取消
I'll do whatever you want.
无论你让我做什么（我都答应你）
Karl put the ball in susan's court...
Karl将决定权交给Susan
with your D.U.I. Charge,it could get ugly.
鉴于你的酒后驾车记录 会让你很难堪
While andrew tried to take bree to court...
Andrew要在法庭上与Bree兵戎相见
- there's a father. - He's a kid!
她有爸爸 他只是一个孩子
Gabrielle and carlos took the baby...
Gabrielle和Carlos得到了婴儿
the papers aren't valid anymore.
合同已经失效了
Do you really wanna leave this beautiful little girl
你真的想将这个美丽的小宝贝
with that white trash freak show?
留给那个脱衣舞娘？
And ran with it.
带着她跑掉
louisa pate believed in the power of shame.
Louisa Pate是位严师
As a teacher,she had found that the best way to control unruly students
她发现教育不守规矩 学生最好的办法
was to instill a strong sense of shame...
就是在他们父母身上
in their parents.
建立一种强烈的羞辱感
I left trisha alonewith the school hamster for only five minutes.
我不过离开Trisha和学校的仓鼠5分钟
In this boxis all that's left of patches.
这个盒子里只剩下一些残骸
For show and tell,timmy decidedto bring in something
为了炫耀，Timmy带来了一些东西
from your husband's collection of nazi memorabilia.
是你丈夫收集的纳粹纪念品
Billy's been threateningto beat up the other kids for their milk money.
Billy通过威胁揍其他小孩的方法 拿走他们的午餐费
We found the proceedsin his cubby.
在他的橱柜我们找到了这些现金
Of course,mrs. Pate also knew when it came to unruly children,
当然,Pate夫人知道 对于一些不守规矩的学生
some parents had more reason to be ashamed...
一些家长更有理由感到羞愧
So,um...
所以
your message saidthat parker had been involved in some sortof serious incident.
你说Parker牵涉到某些很严重的事件
What--what kindof incident?
什么  什么类型的事件
Yesterday afternoon,
昨天下午
parker offered a cookieto cindy lou peeples if she wouldshow him her vagina.
Parker说如果Cindy lou Peeples 肯让他看私处 那他就给冰激凌
What kind of cookie?
什么点心
What does that matter?
有什么关系吗
Oh,it doesn'T.
哦，当然没有
I'm just stalling
一时失语而已
becauseI am completely mortified.
因为我太震惊了
The kids were in a broom closet.
他们躲在一个清洁工具间里
Our janitor walked in on them just as cindy was lifting up her pinafore.
我们的管理员进去时 刚好看到Cindy掀起了她的裙子
Oh,my goodness.
我的天阿
I'm sure you've noticedhow obsessive parker can be.
你也知道parker很顽固
A certain subjectwill catch his interest,
如果一个事物引起了他的兴趣
and that's all he'll talk aboutfor weeks and weeks.
他将会在接下来的几周不停的谈论它
Oh,right.That happened with dinosaurs.
是的，以前他对恐龙痴迷时就是这样
Oh,yes,we all rememberhis dinosaur phase.
对阿，我们都记得他的恐龙痴迷期
More fondly now than ever.
这次更麻烦了
so you thinkthat now he's obsessed with...
所以你认为他现在沉溺于……的问题
what's underneaththe pinafore. Yes.
在裙子下是什么，是的
Look,I thinkhe's just developed a normal curiosity about the human body.
我认为他只不过是 对人体产生了正常的好奇心而已
You need to talk to him.
你需要和他谈谈
Remind him what's appropriateand what isn'T.
提醒他什么是适当的好奇而什么不是
Of course.I will talk to him.
当然，我会和他谈谈
I'll talk to himtill I'm blue in the face.
哪怕动怒了,也要说
I promise.
我保证
Take care.
保重
Yes,louisa pate believed in the power of shame.
是的Louisa Pate喜欢羞辱人
She always believed,when someone has that power...
她相信，当某人有这种权力时
so,mrs. Peeples,
那么,Peeples夫人
you'll never guess what your daughter is willingto do for a gingersnap.
你恐怕猜不出你的女儿 会为了冰激凌做什么
It's a shame not to use it.
不使用它是可耻的
The Desperate Housewives
绝望的主妇
Season 02  Episode 19
第2季 第19集
DON'T LOOK AT ME
不要看着我
It had been six weeks
从andrew van de kamp
since andrew van de kamp had declared war
对他的母亲Bree
on his mother bree.
宣战开始已经过去了六周了
The final battle was about to be waged at the fairview county courthouse.
最终战役将在郡法院展开
Bree knew it was about to get bloody.
Bree知道将会两败俱伤
What she didn't know was...
但是她不知道的是
the calvary was on its way...
末日即将到来
bree?
Bree
Whether she wanted them there or not.
不论她是否欢迎他们的到来
Eleanor!
Oh,thank god I found you.
哦，感谢上帝，我找到你了
This place is a maze.
这个地方像迷宫一样
What are you doing here?
你来这里干什么
Well,your father and I got a call last night from danielle,
是这样，你的父亲和我 昨晚接到了Danielle的电话
and she said that andrew was taking you to court.
她说Andrew起诉你
I mean,to say that we were shocked would be an understatement.
我们太震惊了
Hello,I'm eleanor mason,
你好，我是Eleanor Mason
bree's stepmother.
bree的继母
You're the lawyer? We should talk.
你是律师吗 我们需要谈谈
Uh,no,I'm not her lawyer.
哦，不是，我不是她的律师
Good. The hair had me worried.
太好了，你的头发让我担心来着
Peter is mom's sponsor from A.A.
Peter是妈妈AA会议的联系人
Oh,sweetie!
哦，亲爱的
since when are you in A.A.?
何时开始你参加AA会议
It's a recent development. Where's dad?
最近而已，爸爸去了哪里？
In chambers with the judge.
和法官在会议室里
What?! Why?
什么 为什么
Everything is fine.
一切都搞定了
The judge agreed to a postponement.
法官同意延期
Oh,thank god!
哦，感谢上帝
Luckily,he remembered me.
幸运的是他是一个熟人
I spoke once at his law school.
我在他的法学院做过讲演
Pardon me,sir,
请原谅，先生
I'm your daughter's lawyer.
我是你女儿的律师
Just so you know,we've been waiting for this hearing for weeks,
只是你需要知道 为这次听证我们已经等了几周了
son,I've been an attorney for 45 years.
小伙子，我当律师45年了
You and I both know how these cases can turn into public spectacles.
你我都知道这类案件 会多么的吸引眼球
Our family is perfectly capable of handling this
我们的家庭有能力在内部处理好
- ...in house. - Dad,you don't understand.
爸爸，你不知道
This has gotten really ugly.
事情变得很难以收拾
That's why we're here.
这是我们来这里的原因
We're gonna put this family back together.
我们要将这个家庭重新团结起来
Whatever it takes.
不论什么代价
and that's when mr. And mrs. Solis,
那是为何Solis夫妇
fearing for the welfare of this helpless child,
担心这个无助的孩子的幸福
fled the hospital.
离开了医院
You mean,they kidnapped her.
你是说他们绑架了她
Well,technically,that's true,but
技术上，是的
given the situation that led up to the rescue...
但是考虑到他们的行为是解救
kidnapping.
绑架
Your honor,yes,
法官大人，是的
in retrospect,the plan was a little bit rash, not entirely well thought out.
他们并没有计划，很匆忙的
Idiotic.
愚蠢
can we object to that?
我们能说"反对"吗
But the child is safe,your honor.
但是婴儿是安全的，法官大人
And all we ask the court is to allow baby lily
我们请求法庭允许将lily
a lifetime of the care and love she has been receiving
交给会一生照顾和爱护她的solis夫妇
As much as your story tugs at my heart,
尽管你的故事很打动我
there is the issue of parental rights.
还是有相关的监护权问题
What does the state have to say about this?
对此州检察官有何意见吗
We have located the biological father-- mr. Dale helm.
我们找到了生父，Dale helm先生
Unfortunately,uh,circumstances require that he be out of town.
不巧的是，他现在不在城里
He's in fort lauderdale today.
他今天在fort lauderdale
On business?
商务旅行？
Spring break,actually.
实际上是春假
Mr. Helm is a high school student.
Helm先生是一个高中生
Charming.
有趣
In between keg stands,
在争夺中
did the father happen to mention if he plans to waive parental rights?
这位父亲是否有计划行使监护权呢
I've left a number of voice mails,
我留下了一些语音信息
but the only response I've gotten is a text message
但只得到了一条短信息的回复
that says
他说
this "blows his mind" and he's extremely "bummed out."
他十分吃惊,沮丧
All right...
好了
mr. And mrs. Solis,
Solis先生和夫人
since you actually want lily,
鉴于你们十分关心lily,
it seems you're the lesser of two evils.
两害相权取其轻
I'm granting you temporary custody until
我将赋予你们临时的监护权
we can get a straight answer from the birth father.
直到我们从这个生父 那里得到明确的答覆
Thank you,
谢谢
uh,your honor.
法官大人
In the meantime, try not to steal any more babies.
与此同时，不要再偷婴儿了
Oh,we just needed the one.
哦，我们只需要这一个
sweetie?
亲爱的
Um,could you put the crayons down for a second?
能否将蜡笔先放心几秒钟
We need to talk.
我们需要谈谈
So I spoke to your teacher today,
今天我去见了你的老师
and she told me about the...
她和我说了……
cookie deal you made with cindy lou.
你和cindy lou的冰激凌交易
Oh. Are you mad?
哦，你生气了吗
no,not exactly.
不，没有
I'm just...
我只是
I'm trying to understand why you...
我只是想知道，为何你
did that.
要那样做
Tommy keenan told me babies come from down there.
Tommy keenan告诉我婴儿从那里出来
It doesn't sound right to me.
我不是很理解
Well...
这样
actually,he's kinda right. He's got the concept down.
实际上，他有一点点对 他的概念没错
That's weird.
那就很奇怪了
How's a baby get in there?
婴儿是怎么到那里去的
Daddy will be home from his business trip in a few days.
你的爸爸还有几天 商务旅行就回来了
Why don't you wait for him?
为何你不等他回来告诉你
- Okay. - Okay.
好的 好的
Or I can ask tommy's brother.
或者我去问tommy的哥哥
He's 14,
他14岁了
and he knows everything.
他什么都知道
And then the mommy and the daddy,
然后妈妈和爸爸
because they love each other so much,
因为他们很爱彼此
they hug.
他们拥抱
Real tight.
十分紧密
And,uh,a seed is magically implanted.
然后一个种子就神奇的植入
and nine months later...
九个月后
a baby is born. Here.
一个婴儿就出生了，就在这里
What kind of seed?
什么种类的种子
Oh,that's not important.
哦，那不重要
I don't believe you.
我不相信你
Parker,I'm your mother.
Parke，我是你的母亲
Mothers don't lie to their sons.
母亲不会对她们的孩子撒谎的
Now go wash your hands or santa's not gonna bring youanything for christmas.
去洗手吧，否则圣诞老人 不会给你任何圣诞礼物了
I just saw edie drive off.
我看到edie驾车离开了
How long is she gonna be gone?
她要出去多久？
I don't know.She just went to show a house.
我不知道，她去介绍一个房产
Move.
让开
What's the problem?
什么事情
You mauled mein edie's bed last night.
昨晚在Edie的床上你强吻了我
I think that deservesa conversation.
我认为需要谈谈
Well,what's there to talkabout? I'm just a fool in love.
有什么需要谈的 我只是一个陷入爱河的傻瓜
Oh,no!You don't mean that.
哦，不 你不是真的那么想
Yes,I do.
是的，我是
Look,I realizemy timing's a little off.
看，我意识到时机有点晚了
a little?
一点点？
Ugh...
啊
the helium hasn't evengone out of the balloons from your engagement party.
你的订婚派对气球还没有瘪呢
okay...
好的
when are you gonna tell edie?
你打算什么时候告诉Edie?
Tell her what?
告诉她什么
- That the wedding's off. - Is it?
婚礼取消了 是吗
- Well,isn't it? - It's up to you.
不是吗 由你决定
Are... are you saying...
你，你是说……
that you're gonnago through with this wedding...
我不要你结婚
unless I tell you not to?
你就不结婚了?
Just give me a commitment,susie Q.,
只要你给我一个承诺，susie Q
And I'll put a bullet in edie.
我会抛弃Edie
This is insane!
这太疯狂了
Come on.
想想吧
All thiscan be yours again.
我们会鸳梦重温
Just say the word...
只要你说一句
and I let go.
我就会放手
Oh,no!No,don't you dare!
哦，不，不 你敢
You know you want me to.Just say it,susie Q.
你知道你想我这么做 说吧，susie Q
You're...
你太
sick!
变态了
zach,I'm going to the drugstore.
zach我去药房一下
I'll be back in 20 minutes.
20分钟后回来
Whoa! Oh!
啊，哦
I was making cookies, and iheard the most sickening thud.
我正在做甜饼，听到了最懵懂的一声
Are you okay?
你还好么?
There'S...
门前有...
shortening on my doorstep.
酥油
Shortening?
酥油?
That's the last thingyou'd want on your front porch.
那是最不想门廊上有的东西
It's meant for baking.
只有烤甜饼时候用
She's so adorable
她太可爱了
and I just love the name Lily
我喜欢Lily这个名字
it wasmy grandmother's name.
我祖母的名字
So how you holding up?You must be exhausted.
你怎么撑过来的？一定累坏了
You know,I'm a little tired, but it's not too bad.
有些累，但并不太糟
Oh,wait a couple months. She'll startsleeping through the night.
几个月后，她就可以睡好觉了
Oh,honey,please.Do I look like a masochist?
拜托，我像受虐狂么？
Firs thing tomorrow, I'm hiringa nanny and a night nurse.
明天的第一件事 就是雇保姆和夜间看护
No,we're not.
不，我们不雇
my husband,the comedian.
我丈夫是个喜剧演员
I'm serious. I don't wantsome stranger raising our baby.
我是认真的 我不想让陌生人抚养孩子
Well,you guys are busy.We should go.
你们很忙，我们该走了
No,it's okay.I'll win this battle later.
没关系，以后翻盘
We are not gonna besome yuppie couple pawning off our kid on otherpeople.
我们不会像雅皮士把孩子当给别人
- End of discussion.
- 讨论结束.
Yeah,you should go.
是啊，你们该走了
Yeah.Okay,bye.
OK，再见
Good luck.
好运
put down the burrito.
放下煎饼
What is all this crapabout me not getting help?
为什么不让我找帮手?
Look,a brand-new babyneeds to bond with its mother.
新生儿要和母亲接触
The church knows it,scienceknows it,nature knows it.
教堂知道，科学家知道 自然界也知道
We have the money. What is wrong with getting a little help?
我们有钱 找一点帮助有什么不对呢？
Then I'll be ableto relax once in a while,
我就可以休息一下
and I'll be ableto be a better mother.
成为更好的母亲
You wanna bea better mother?
你想成为更好的母亲？
Do what my mam* did--
像我妈妈一样--
make sacrifices.
做出牺牲
My mam* worked her fingers to the bone for me.
我妈妈为我拚死拚活
And that's what put herin an early grave!
因此她才短命
Well,thatand the hit-and-run thing.
实际上是她被撞的
look,I don't know whyyou want to be emancipated,
我不知道你为什么想独立
and I don't know what you'v been doing to drive him crazy.
也不知道你为什么让他发疯
Bottom line--
底线是--
it's over.
都结束了
It's now time for you twoto kiss and make up.
是你们言归于好的时候了
And just howare we supposed to do that?
那要怎么做？
Here's a thought...
是这样...
just look each otherin the eye and say,
看着对方的眼睛，说
"I forgive you."
"我原谅你"
that's your solution?
那是你的方法?
It's actuallya technique invented by this dutch therapist.
事实上是一个荷兰医生发明的方法
I saw him on tv.
我在电视上看到
He says,if you verbalize forgiveness,
他说，如果你们口头上原谅
the brain can trick the heart in to letting go of resentment.
大脑可以欺骗心灵 丢弃一切怨恨
It really works. I did it with our cleaning lady.
很有效，我和保姆用过
Um,I'm sorry,dad, but I think my relationship with andrew
对不起，不过我觉得和Andrew的关系
- is just a bit more complicatedthan--
- 更复杂一些...
would it kill youto at least try?
试一下会死么?
I'll do it...
我做...
for you,grandpa.
为你，爷爷
That's my boy.
这才是我孙子
Bree?
Bree？
Fine!
好!
Yes,um...
是的，嗯...
so,um,who goes first?
那么谁先来?
Either or.Doesn't matter.
都行，没关系
Mom,
妈妈,
I forgive you.
我原谅你
Andrew,
Andrew
I forgive you.
我原谅你
That wasn't so hard,was it?
并不难，不是么？
Now don't expectto feel differently right away.
先别期望有什么变化
It takes a while.
需要时间
It took me a weekto forgive esperanza.
我原谅Esperanza花了1星期
But now she's like family again.
但她现在像个家人了
Family who stole from us.
偷东西的家人
So let's get backto the way we were,
让我们回到原先
and forget all this nonsenseabout emancipation.
忘了什么"独立"的蠢话
Um...
呃...
well,grandpa,I'm--I'm stillgonna need my trust fund.
爷爷，我还是需要信托基金
You see,I-I can't live in a place where I...
我不能生活在...
I don't feel safe.
我感到不安全
What are you talking about?
你说什么?
Well,could you livewith a woman who hits you?
你能和打人的妈妈住一起么？
- Bree!
I slapped him once,and he deserved it.
我扇过一巴掌，他应得的
Well,I just asked herto stop drinking.
我只是让她别酗酒
You were drinking?
你在酗酒?
She's in A.A.Her sponsor has long hair.
她参加了A.A 她的监督人留长发
Andrew,I find your concern ironic,
Andrew,我发现你的想法很讽刺
given how tanked you werewhen you ran over our neighbor's motherwith your car.
考虑到，你曾怎样醉醺醺地 开车碾过邻居的母亲
Is she okay?
她还好么?
She's dead!
她死了!
mom watched as her boyfriendcommitted suicide.
妈妈在男友自杀时坐视不管
And he was the same guy who killed dad!
也是他杀死爸爸
Andrew falsely accused meof molestation...
Andrew错误地告我性骚扰...
in a mall!
在商场里!
You know,the technique works best if you don't talk right away.
先保持沉默 刚才的方法才奏效
Okay,let's go.
好，我们走
I don't wannabe late for the movie.
我不想电影迟到
Oh,those are pretty.Who sent those?
这些很漂亮，谁送的？
What?
什么?
"Say the word and I'm yours.Love,karl."
"说出来我就属于你，爱你的Karl"
Mom,I knew this would happen when you started hanging around together,
妈,我知道你们相处时
all of your old feeling sresurfacing.
旧时的感觉会重现
No,his feelings.
不,他的感觉
He's the one with the feelings,not me.
他是有感觉的,不是我
Uh-huh.
阿哈
Okay,don't "uh-huh" me. You'renot old enough to do that.
好,不要"啊哈" 你年纪还不够
Oh,no?Well,how do you like this--
是么?你觉得这个怎样
I'm not gonna go to the movies with you.
我不和你去看电影
You're gonna make mego by myself?
你要我自己去?
Well,you could alwaysask dad to go.
你可以叫爸爸去
In fact,if you love him so much, why don't you marry him?
事实上,如果你这么爱他 为什么不嫁给他?
Oh,wait,you already did. Twice.
等等,你已经嫁了 两次
Oh,you know what? I think we're gonna need some napkins with this.
我觉得需要些纸巾
Oh,okay,I'll go back.
好,我去拿
Thanks.
谢谢
My ex-boyfriend's here. If he sees me alone,I'll die.
前男友看到我一个人 我会死掉
I'm begging you,please, act like you know me.
求你装作认识我
Susan? Hey!
Susan? 嘿!
Mike,hi! what a surprise.
Mike,hi! 真巧
How are ya?Good.
你怎样？ 很好
Oh!God,I--I'm being so rude.
天，我真无礼
Um,mike,I-I want you to meet...
Mike，介绍你认识...
orson hodge.
Orson Hodge.
Nice to meet you,mike.
高兴见到你，Mike
Wow,I can't believe I'm finally seeing the man himself in the flesh.
喔，不敢相信终于见到真人
So... how'd you two meet?
那么，你们怎么认识的？
Oh,god,I've beenher dentist for years.
我做她的牙医好多年了
but last week,I was looking in her mouth
而上个星期，我看着她的嘴
and decidedto stick my tongue in it.
于是决定伸舌头进去
I'll see ya,susan.
以后见,Susan
thank you so muchfor helping me out.
非常感谢帮忙
Hey,I'm great in a crisis.
我善于处理危机
well,I definitely pickedthe right person to sit next to.
我一定选对了人
Actually,is this seat taken?
事实上，这里有人么？
- No.
- 没有
Okay,you can sharemy popcorn.
好，你可以吃爆米花
Um,susan...
呃，Susan...
this is becky.
这是Becky.
I'll probably be sharing her popcorn.
大概要吃她的爆米花
I'll just waittill the lights go out, and then I'll...
等到熄灯，我就....
while I get this going,can you bring out the buns?
等我弄好了，把面包拿出来
Uh,yeah.
好
- what the hell?
- 怎么回事
You all right?
你还好么？
This isn't lighter fluid.It's gasoline.
不是打火机油，是汽油
What?
什么?
How'd that get in there?
怎么搞的?
How do you think?
你觉得呢？
Something smells goodover there.
闻起来很香
Well,I don't understand.
我不明白
Is she trying to kill you?
她想杀死你？
No,she's tryingto piss me off.
不，她想惹毛我
Why?
为什么?
I'm not sure yet,
不确定
but I do knowI'm not gonna play along.
我可不奉陪了
We got plenty of burgersif you want to pop over.
有很多汉堡包，想来拜访么
And bring your appetite.
带着胃口来
gaby,the baby.
Gaby,孩子
No,I got up twice already.It's your turn.
不，我已经起来2次了 该你了
Gaby,I have severaljob interviews tomorrow. I need my sleep.
Gaby,我明天有面试，需要睡眠
What about my sleep?
那我的睡眠呢？
You sleepwhen the baby sleeps.
孩子睡觉的时候你再睡觉
Every 40 minutes? When am I supposedto have a life?
每40分钟？ 我什么时候才能有正常生活？
What are you whining about?
你在发什么牢骚？
You know,xiao-mei doesall the housework around here.
你知道，xiao-mei做了家里所有的家务
All you have to dois take care of the baby.
你所要做的仅仅是照顾孩子
Fine,fine,fine!
好，好，好！
xiao-mei.
xiao-mei
wake up.
醒醒
Mrs. Solis?
Solis太太？
Something wrong?
发生什么事了么？
the baby won't stop crying, and I haven't sleptfor two days.
baby不能止住哭声，我两天都没睡觉了
Will you please take lily for a while?
你能带一会lily么？
oh,come on. I won't make youdo windows tomorrow.
哦，来吧。我明天不会让你擦窗户了
Okay.
好吧
What do I do?
我能做什么？
Well,she's a baby.You hold her.
是这样，她是个小婴儿，你抱着她
You bounce her and, I don't know, maybe sing a little something.
你拍拍她，我不知道 也许你可以唱首歌
Ahh.
啊
Oh,and xiao-mei,
哦，还有，xiao-mei
mr. Solis does not need to know about this,okay?
Solis先生不需要知道这些，明白么？
- Okay. - Okay.
好的，好的
yeah,honey,can youtake that downstairs?
你能去楼下吗?
Thank you.
谢谢
Eleanor,I thought you'd gone to bed.
Eleanor,我以为你睡了
Oh,no,not yet.I had to do my hair now.
没呢,我还要做头发
There's never enough timein the morning.
早上没时间的
Uh,sit.
坐吧
There's somethingI have to discuss with you.
我想和你讨论点事
Your father and ihave decided to take an drew back to rhode islandwith us.
你父亲和我要带andrew回罗德岛
Really?
是吗?
And whose idea was that?
谁的主意?
Andrew'S.
Andrew的
But henry and I feelit's the right thing to do.
我们觉得这样做是正确的
Absolutely not.
绝对不是
If we leave him here,
如果我们把他留下
the two of youwill wind up in court,
你们最终会闹上法庭
and I'm notgoing to allow that.
我不会允许它发生
Do you really think that I am enjoying airing my dirty laundry in public?
你真以为我喜欢把家丑外扬?
This whole situationis mortifying.
局势能控制住
But I can't back downbecause he is my son,
但不能因为他是我儿子就屈服
and I need more timeto get through to him.
我需要时间和他沟通
You never give up.
你从不放弃
I've always admired thatabout you.
我一直很欣赏你这一点
When you were a kid,
你小的时候
you used to makethese peanut butter cookies that were god-awful.
做的花生酱饼干就难以下咽
But you kept baking them,
但你还要做
and you kept forcing everyoneto eat them.
一直在强迫所有人吃
you were so determinedto get them right.
你决意要把它们做好
My mother didn't thinkthey were awful.
我妈妈认为它们不难吃
When I made those same cookiesfor her,
当我给她做同样的饼干时
she loved them.
她很喜欢
Well,some peoplepraise children even whenthey don't deserve it.
一些人总是表扬他们的孩子 不管这些孩子值不值得表扬
Oh,but not you.
哦，但你不是这样
With you,I had to work for every kind word I ever got.
和你在一起，我不得不字斟句酌
Well,you always resented mebecause of my high standards.
我知道， 你一直因为我对你的高标准而怨恨我
No.
不
I resented you because those were kick-asspeanut butter cookies.
我怨恨你是因为那些是很好吃的黄油饼干
We're taking andrew.
我们在说andrew
Eleanor,please...
Eleanor，求你了
he hates you,bree.
他恨你，bree
Your own son.
你自己的儿子
You know,part of being an adult is admitting
你知道，作为一个成年人 就不得不接受这样一个事实
that you've failed, and then moving on...
失败了，再继续向前
with grace.
优雅的
Do you really think that I ama failure as a parent?
你真的认为我是一个失败的母亲？
well,I'd love to lieand say something supportive,
好吧，我愿意说谎，说一些支持的话
but as you pointed out,
但就像你所说的
that was moreyour mother's thing.
那更多是你做母亲的问题
Xiao-mei?
Xiao-mei？
So sorry.I just take break.
对不起，我刚休息了一会
Oh,no,xiao-mei,that's okay.
oh，不，xiao-mei，没事的
That's okay. I know you were up all nightwith the baby,
没事的。我知道你一晚上都和宝宝在一起
and I reallyappreciate it.
我非常的感激
You know,I'm very grateful for everythingyou've been doing for lily.
你知道，我感激你为lily做的每一件事
So to thank you,I bought your gift certificate to my spa.
为了感谢你 我给你买了张spa卡作为礼物
And you can take a whole day offand just really pamper yourself.
你可以休息一整天，放松一下
- Really?
- 真的？
Mm-hmm.
唔
Thank you!
谢谢你！
Oh,thank you!
哦，谢谢你！
Oh,you're welcome.
哦，没关系
All right,lily needsto be bathed and put to bed.
好吧，lily需要洗澡、睡觉
I don't wanna missmy yoga class.
我不想错过我的瑜伽学习班
Hi. Hi,pretty girl.
嗨，漂亮姑娘
Oh,yes,mommy has to go.
哦，是的。妈妈要走了
Mommy has to go,
妈妈要走了
so she can stay pretty and thin and you can be proud of her.
这样她才能保持漂亮又苗条 你也可以以她为荣
motherhoodis such a blessing.
做母亲真好
I hope you getto experience it one day.
希望有一天你也拥能有这种体验
becauseit's not a big deal!
因为这不算什么！
- "it's not a big deal"? Okay!
- “这不算什么”？好吧！
It's not that far away.
这不算太远
- Right. Oh,it's notthat far away?
- 对。是的，不算太远？
Dude,it--whatever,okay?
哥们，它——随它怎么样吧
You didn't even care to tell me before?Bye.
你以前怎么不告诉我？再见
justin,what happened?
justin，怎么啦？
Andrew just told me he'smoving in with his grandparents.
Andrew刚告诉我 他要和他外公外婆一起搬走
They live so far away, I'm never gonnasee him anymore.
他们住的那么远，我再也见不到他了
I'm so sorry. I know that you're good friends.
我很抱歉，我知道你们是好朋友
We're more than friends,mrs. Van de kamp.
我们不只是朋友，太太
I love him.
我爱他
Oh.
哦
Why?
为什么？
Yes.I'd be curious to know just what it isyou see in him.
是的，我很好奇你怎么看待他
Well,when my parentsfirst heard I was gay, they kicked me out.
好吧，当我父母第一次听说我是同性恋 他们把我赶出了家门
They said I had debasedthe entire family
他们说我令整个家族蒙羞
and that they couldn'tlove me anymore until I changed.
他们不会再爱我了，除非我痛改前非
But andrew--
但是andrew——
he said that i should be ashamed of them,
他说我应该为他们感到羞愧
'cause they were too stupidto know how great I was.
因为他们太愚蠢以至于看不出我的伟大
That's the thingabout andrew.
andrew就是这样的人
He doesn't take crapfrom anyone. How can you notlove someone like that?
他心里没有任何人 你怎么会爱他这样的人？
You know,it never ceases to amaze me
你知道，我一直感到惊奇
how people can turn their backson their own family.
人们怎么会不热爱自己的家庭
I mean--but it happensevery day,doesn't it?
我是说——但是这种事情 每天都在发生，不是吗？
I guess.
我猜
You know,justin,if youwould be willing to help,
你知道，justin，如果你肯帮忙
I'm pretty sure that I could find a way to keep andrew from moving.
我一定能找到办法阻止andrew离开
What do you say?
你说什么？
I'm home.
我到家了
- Oh,hi.
- 哦，嗨
Hey,mrs. Mccluskey.
嘿，Mccluskey太太
So how did everything go?
一切都还好吧？
Fine.
很好
Penny fussed a bit.
penny有点大惊小怪
I think her molars are coming in.
我想她开始长牙了
Oh.
哦
And the twinsfought over the remote. There's nothing new there.
双胞胎在为争抢遥控器而厮打 这里没有什么新鲜事
No.
不
here's the big news--
这里有条大新闻——
parker offered me a fudgsicleif I would show him my vagina.
parker说如果我给他看我的私处 他就把他的冰激凌给我吃
Oh,good god,lynette,relax.I didn't do it.
oh，上帝，lynette，放松。 我没有那么干
I just got thisout of the freezer a second ago.
我刚从冰箱里拿出来
Uh,yeah. Of course.No,sorry.
uh，是的。当然。不，对不起
Apparently,parker wanted to puta sunflower seed inside me
显然，parker想放一颗 向日葵的种子到我的身体里
and see if a baby would grow.
看看是不是会有宝宝长出来
Where do kids get this stuff?
孩子们是从哪里知道这些的？
Oh... that was me.
oh……是我
He was asking aboutthe birds and the bees, and I
他问有关两性关系的基本常识，我
fudgeda few of the details.
捏造了一些细节
Well,he's only 7 years old.
好吧，他只有7岁
I don't think he needsto know everything yet.
我认为他还不需要知道所有事情
I don't wanna rob himof his innocence.
我不想让他失去天真的本性
Well,now,that's where you're wrong.
好吧，现在，这就是你的不对了
You get 'emwhen they're young.
你在他们年轻的时候
Give themall the gory details.
告诉他们一些血淋淋的细节
And then when they're goodand disgusted,you shame 'em.
当他们长大独立了 你会为他们感到可耻
Excuse me?
对不起？
You tell themsex is dirty and wrong and he shouldn'ttalk about it,
你告诉他们性是肮脏可耻的 他们不应该谈论
and if he does,he's going straight to hell.
如果他们谈论了，就会直接下地狱
that is ridiculous.
这太荒谬了
Spoken likea true liberal idiot.
说起话来真像是个真正的自由主义白痴
No,I'm notgonna shame my son.
不，我不会为我的儿子感到羞愧
Mm,I'm telling ya,it works.
嗯，我告诉你，这有效果
It keeps peoplein their place,
它让人们呆在他们应该呆的地方
it keeps parentsfrom being humiliated,
它使得父母避免丢脸
and it keeps me fromhaving to spend the afternoon talking about my woo-woo.
他使得我免得 用一个下午来谈论我的私处
In your haste to duck out before the credits rolled,you...
你匆忙离开的时候，你...
oh,my god!Oh,thank you so much.
哦，我的上帝！哦，太谢谢你啦
I stuck a card in there,
我留了张名片
just in case you ever wanted to purposely sit next to meat a movie,so...
万一你想出来吃个饭，看场电影，就...
orson,I'm flattered.Uh,really.
哦，我很荣幸。真的
you--you don't wanna date me.
你——你不会想和我约会吧
I-I mean,my love life is justso complicated right now.
我...我是说 我的感情生活目前真的很混乱
Well... no,I won't bore youwith the details.
好吧...不，我不想用细节来让你厌烦
So the ex-boyfriend has no idea you're secretly married to the ex-husband,
那么你的前男友对于你 和你的前夫结婚一无所知
who still loves you,
那个仍然爱着你的前夫
but unless you give hima reason not to,
但是除非你给他一个理由
is gonna marrythe neighborhood slut?
不用去和荡妇邻居结婚？
Did I call edie a slut?
我有称edie是一个荡妇？
Well,that's overstating it.Edie's not a slut.
好吧，这有点夸张了 edie不是一个荡妇
She's just... popularwith indiscriminate men.
她只是...对于男人不加选择
Anyway...
不管怎么说...
yes,those arethe relevant players.
是的，这些都是有关的人
Okay.
好吧
Now I'm absolutelyhorrified that I'm about to saywhat I'm about to say,
现在我对自己即将 说出的话感到十分恐惧
but there's nobody else I cantalk to who won't judge me.
但是再没有谁是既能让我倾吐心声 又不会对我妄加评判的人了
And sinceyou're a complete stranger, I'll probablynever see you again
由于你是一个完全的陌生人 我很可能再也见不到你了
unless I randomlyrun into you on the street,
除非我在马路上偶然遇见你
in which case,you'll ignore me 'cause you know how crazy I am.
在那种情况下，你会无视我 因为你知道我有多疯狂
So here goes...
所以我要告诉你……
I'm having feelingsfor karl again.
我又对karl有感觉了
does that make mea terrible person?
这样会不会显得我是个可怕的人？
You wantmy unvarnished opinion?
你需要我朴实的建议吗？
Lay it on me.
说吧
It doesn't make youa terrible person,
这没有显得你是个可怕的人
but it does make you A...
但是这的确使你显得是个……
well... a sucker.
好吧...一个糟糕的人
This karl's a coward.
这个karl是一个懦夫
He wants you to be the heavy and take all the responsibility.
他想把负担给你，让你对一切负责
If you're having feelings for a guy like that, I say run
如果你对这样的人有感觉 我说还是快跑吧
...far,far away.
跑得越远越好
He lives three houses down.
他就住在三幢房子外
Hmm.Well,good luck to you,then.
嗯，好吧，那么祝你好运
but like I said,if you're interested in a tooth whitening,
但是就像我说的， 如果你对于牙齿美白有兴趣
my card'sstill in your wallet.
我的名片就在你的钱包里
Xiao-mei?
Xiao-mei？
I'm late to meetmrs. Van de kamp.
我去见Van de kamp太太要迟到了
I'll be backin a little while.
我一会就回来
bree...I'm so sorry I'm late.
bree……对不起我迟到了
Oh,honey,it's all right.
oh，甜心，没事的
I mean,with the new baby at home, I'm surprisedyou made it at all.
我是说，房子里有个宝宝，我很惊讶 你把一切都打理得井井有条
Ooh,I'll have a drink. Anything with an umbrella.
哦，我要杯喝的。 任何有把小伞的饮料
So tell me,how are you doing?
那么告诉我，你还好吗？
I mean,your entire world must be turned upside down.
我是说，你的世界一定天翻地覆了
You must be exhausted.
你肯定累坏了
You know,it's been challenging, but I-I soldier on. (Chuckles)
你知道，这很有挑战性 但是我——我撑下来了
so what about you?You look so rested.
那你怎么样？你看起来休息的不错
I just got a massageat misty spring.
我刚在misty spring做了一个按摩
Things have beena little tense at home, and I needed an hourto relax.
家里的事情有点紧张 我需要一个小时来放松放松
Good for you.I love that spa.
这对你很好，我爱那个spa
oh,by the way,while I was there, I saw your,uh,
oh，顺便说一句， 我在那里的时候，我看到了你的，呃
your housekeeper.
你的管家
Xiao-mei?
Xiao-mei？
Oh,no,you must be mistaken. I just left her.
oh，不，你肯定搞错了，我刚刚离开她
She's at home working.
她在家里工作
Are you sure? I was talking to her in the steam room for about 20 minutes.
你肯定吗？我在蒸汽房和她谈了有20分钟
- What?
- 什么？
Yeah,
是的
apparently you gave hera gift certificate.
显然你给了她一张卡作为礼物
lily?
lily？
Lily,mommy's coming!
Lily，妈妈来了！
Oh,thank god!Oh,honey,I'm so sorry.
oh，感谢上帝！oh，甜心，我很抱歉
I'm never gonnaleave you again. Oh!
我再也不会离开你了。哦！
Yes. Yes.
是的。是的
I'm home!
我到家了！
My interview got canceled.
我的采访取消了
oh,that's my little girl.
oh，那是我的小女孩
Your chakra lining up nicefor mommy?
想妈妈了么？
That's my girl.
真是我的乖孩子
hey,let me take her off your chest so you can do your yoga.
hey，让我把她从你胸口拿下来 这样你就可以做你的瑜伽了
No! No,no,no.We're doing just fine.
不！不，不，不。我们做的很好
Aren't we,lily?
是不是，lily？
bridezilla's got meauditioning wedding bands,
bridezilla让我试听了一些婚礼乐队
and I'm clueless aboutedie's taste in music.
我对edie的音乐品味没有语言了
What do you thinkof these guys?
你认为这些家伙怎么样？
That's why you brought me down here?
那就是你叫我来这里的原因？
Karl,you made it sound likeit was an emergency.
karl，你听起来像有急事
It is! I need to have somebodyto dance with
这是急事！我需要一个舞伴
so I can see if these guys have the power to help me get my groove on.
那样我就可以知道这些人是不是 可以调动起我的最佳状态
Karl...uh-oh!
karl……uh-oh！
Oh,that's right.
哦，那就对了
You like it laid-backand romantic,don't you?
你喜欢松弛浪漫的，不是吗？
Guys,can we playsomething mellow?
伙计们，我们可不可以来点柔美的？
No,don't bother,'cause I'm going.
不，不必麻烦了，因为我要走了
two...
二...
- you are so beautiful...
- 你是如此美丽
that was nota coincidence.
这不是一个巧合
This was playingthe night we first kissed.
这是我们初吻的夜晚所演奏的音乐
it's our song. Remember?
这是我们的歌，记得吗？
I remember.
我记得
I also remember that you are planning on marrying someone else.
我还记得你在计划娶另外一个人
Not if you don'twant me to.
如果你不想让我娶的话
Come on,susie Q.
来吧，susie Q
I can see you stillhave feelings for me,
我可以看出你对我还是有感觉的
and I know I havenever stopped loving you.
我也知道我没有停止爱过你
Okay,you want the truth?
Okay，你想知道真相吗？
I don't knowhow I feel about you,
我不知道我对你是什么感觉
but I keep looking at you,
但是我一直看着你
trying to see if you've changed, if you've grown up.
想看看你是不是改变了，是不是成熟了
You know what I see?
你知道我看了什么吗？
I see the same weak coward that walked out on methree years ago.
我看到了仍然是那个 三年前离我而去的懦夫
Of course I've changed.
我当然改变了
I don't think so.
我认为你没有
so I think you shouldprobably stay with edie.
所以我认为你还是和edie在一起比较好
and the band is good.
乐队不错
You should hire 'em.
你应该雇他们
what the hell?
到底怎么回事？
For god's sakes...
看在上帝的份上……
what the hellare you doing in there?!
你到底在那里干什么？！
This is my house.What are you doing?
这是我的房子。你们在干什么？
We're tenting for termites.We got a work order.
我们在灭蚁。我们接到了一个工作订单
Signed by who?
是谁签字的？
Paul...
I've never been so embarrassedin my whole life.
在我的一生中，从来没有这么尴尬
They're supposedto be tenting my house.
他们应该罩起我的房子
I must've writtenthe address down wrong.
我肯定是把地址搞错了
muchachos,mi casa est* aqu?
muchachos,mi casa est* aqu? （西班牙语）
You've taken it too farthis time.
这次你做得太过分了
These little mind gamesare gonna stop
这些小小的头脑游戏应该结束了
right now!
马上！
and ifthey don't,whatcha gonna do?
如果不，你想怎么做？
Blow out your brainslike your wife did?
像你太太一样打爆自己的脑子？
- ahh!
- 啊！
hey,hey!
嘿，嘿！
- Hey,you okay?
- 嘿，你还好吗？
Did you hear that?
你听到了吗？
He assaulted mefor an honest mistake.
他因为我的一个无心之失而攻击我
God knows what would've happened if you hadn't been here.
天晓得如果你们不在的话 他会干什么
Let go!
放开！
Dad,dad,dad.Come on.
爸爸，爸爸，爸爸，走吧
Come on.Come on,okay?
走吧，走吧，okay？
I talked to mrs. Mccluskey, and for god's sakes,parker,
我和Mccluskey太太谈过了 看在上帝的份上，parker
you can't ask people things like that.
你不可以问别人这种事情
Why?
为什么？
Because...
因为……
it's rude.
那样很无礼
I said "please."
我说了“请”
Well,that doesn't matter!
好吧，不是那个的关系！
You gotta quit talkingto people about their bodies,
你不能和别人讨论他们的身体
and about where,you know,babies come from.
谈论那个，宝宝出来的地方
- Why?
- 为什么？
because it's notan appropriate subject.
因为那不是一个合适的话题
Why?
为什么？
Because it's not.
因为那不是
- Why?
- 为什么？
Ugh!
呃！
Because it's dirty and wrong, and I'll wash your mouth outwith soap! That's why.
因为那很肮脏、无耻 我会用肥皂洗你的嘴！
In that moment,
那一刻
lynette saw a look on her son's face she had never seen before...
lynette在她儿子的脸上看到一种 她从未见过的表情
and she thought of the look he had on his face
她想念那种他脸上的表情
when he had become obsessed with dinosaurs...
当他迷上恐龙的时候……
obsessed with baseball
迷上篮球的时候
and obsessed with trains.
迷上火车的时候
And it occurred to lynette
突然之间，lynette意识到
she didn't need to shame her son.
她不必为自己的儿子感到羞愧
All he needed was a brand-new obsession.
他所需要的是对一种新的东西着迷
But I thought you saidwe couldn't have a puppy.
但是我认为你说过 我们不能养小狗的
Well...
好吧……
it turns outwe really needed one.
事实证明我们真的需要一个
You can go and play.
你们可以去玩了
And though she didn't know it at the time,
但是当时她不知道
it would be another three years
过了三年以后
before parker scavo would ever ask about sex again.
parker scavo再也没 问起有关“性”的事情
Karl. What's going on?
karl 怎么啦？
Uh,I'm on my wayto a motel.
uh，我在去汽车旅馆的路上
I-I just wanted to let you know that the wedding is off.
我，我只是想让你知道，婚礼取消了
It is?
是吗？
I told edieI wasn't in love with her--
我告诉edie我爱的不是她——
at least,not in the waythat she deserves.
至少，不是以那种她应得的方式
Wow.
哇
Why did you changeyour mind?
为什么你改变主意了？
I mean,I hope it wasn't because of me, because I told you--
我希望这不是因为我 因为我告诉你——
it wasn't for you.
这不是因为你
No?
不是？
You were right.
你是对的
I have been a coward.
我曾是一个懦夫
I was a coward three years ago
三年前我是个懦夫
when I walked out on the two most important peoplein my life.
我离开了我生命中最重要的两个人
And I was being a cowardwith edie.
和edie在一起时我也是个懦夫
I mean,to even consider marrying her
我是说，甚至考虑娶她
when I know what real passionand real love feels like.
在我知道了什么是 真正的激情和爱情之后
Anyway,I-I-I just thoughtI'd let you know.
无论如何，我、我、我只是想让你知道
Karl...
Karl……
you look pretty beat up.
你看上去很受打击
why--why don't you...why don't you come in and...
为什么——为什么你不…… 为什么你不进来……
we'll crack opena bottle of wine.
我们可以开一瓶酒
Come on.
来吧
All right,here we go.
好吧，我们走
This is the lastof andrew's things.
这是最后一点andrew的东西
Once we tape up these boxes, we can start loading the car.
一旦我们打包好这些盒子 我们就可以开始装车了
I'm proud of you,bree.
我为你骄傲，bree
You're being awfully bigabout this.
你对这件事表现得很大度
Well,I have to admit,I was a bit up set at first.
好吧，我得承认 一开始我是有点不安
But then it hit me.
但是后来这提醒了我
You're his grandparents. You should bond,
你们是他的祖父母 你们有权利
get to know the real andrew.
知道真正的andrew
oh,dad,I-I forgot to warn you.
oh，爸爸，我、我忘记提醒你了
These are someof andrew's adult videos.
这些是andrew的成人录影带
I don't approve,but boys will be boys.
我不赞同，但是男孩子总是那样
Oh,henry,stop looking at that filth.
henry，别盯着这些淫秽的东西看
I don't get it.
我不明白
Where are the women?
女人们都在哪里？
What are you talking about?
你在说什么呢？
This is all just a bunch of...
这只是一堆……
naked men.
裸男
Sweet mother of god.What the hell are they doing?
我的上帝 他们到底在干什么？
I don't know,and I don'teven know what I'm looking at.
我不知道，我甚至不知道我在看什么
Henry,this is pornographyfor ho-homosexuals.
henry，这是针对同性恋的黄书
Oh,shoot! I wish youhadn't gone through that.
天啊！真不希望被你们发现
Now we have to havean unpleasant conversation,
现在我们不得不 来一次不愉快的谈话了
and we were havingsuch a nice time.
我们过得那么开心
is andrew... gay?
bree,andrew是不是……同性恋？
Oh,dad,andrew hates labels.
oh，爸爸，andrew厌恶被贴标签
I'm sure it's just a phase.
我肯定这是一个阶段而已
Excuse me,
对不起
but he has a magazine titled"leather daddies in love."
但是他有一本叫做 “皮衣老爹之恋”的杂志
That does not sound likea phase to me.
那在我看来不像是一个阶段
Maybe not,but it's no longer my concern now that he'll be livingwith you.
不会了，不关我事 他马上就要搬去和你们住了
We have to havea serious talk.
我们要好好的谈谈
Let's don't freak outabout this.
我们不要为此惊慌失措
The dutch therapist says--
荷兰临床医学家说——
forget the dutch therapist!In the kitchen!
别提荷兰临床医学家！到厨房里！
now!
现在！
hey,where's grandma and grandpa?
hey，爷爷奶奶在哪里？
I need to startloading up my stuff.
我要开始装我的东西了
Oh,they,uh,they already left.
他们已经走了
Wait... they left?
等等……他们走了？
Without me?
没有带上我？
Uh,yeah,they wrote you a letter.
是的，他们留给你了一封信
It seems they came across some personal items of yours that, um,
看起来他们发现了一些你的私人物品
upset them.
那些东西让他们很不安
They're taking awaymy trust fund?
他们拿走了我的信托基金？
They can't do that!
他们不能那么做！
Well,actually they can.
好吧，事实上他们可以
I mean,it's their money todispense with as they see fit.
我是说，这是他们的钱 用他们认为合理的方式进行分配
I knowit doesn't seem fair,but--
我知道这看起来不公平，但是——
no,it's really unfair. In fact,it sucks.
不，这就是不公平 事实上，这糟透了
What--what am I supposedto do now?
现在，我该怎么办？
Well,now that you can't afford to become emancipated,
好吧，既然你没有钱支付 自己脱离监管以后的生活了
I guess you're gonnahave to stay here with me.
我猜你要在这里 和我生活一段时间了
Andrew,we can make this work.
andrew，我们可以和平相处的
We just haveto let go of our anger.
我们只是需要抛弃我们的愤怒
No.
不
Oh,I,um,had a chance to have a nice chat with justin the other day.
我，那天我和justin好好谈了一谈
He really seems very sweet.
他看上去真的很好
I've invited him overfor dinner tonight. I hope you don't mind.
我邀请他今晚过来吃晚饭 我希望你不介意
Now I wish I hadn't torched our wedding photos.
现在我希望我没有 把我们的婚礼照片付之一炬
who would've thought, after everythingthat's happened,
谁会想到，经过了那么多事情
that we would'veended up back here again?
我们还能够再一次在一起？
It's beenone hell of a ride,huh?
真是一个漫长的过程，huh？
so how do you feel now?
那你现在感觉怎么样？
About us?
关于我们？
I feel good.
我感觉很好
I feel happy.
我感到高兴
You're not having second thoughts?
你想都没有想就脱口而出？
I can't believe you actually want to talk about feelings.
我不敢相信你真的会谈论感觉
You really have changed.
你真的变了
Hey,this is the new karl,baby.
这是崭新的karl，宝贝
He's not afraid to cry.
他不害怕哭泣
hello?
喂？
oh,hi,edie.
嘿,edie
Uh...
嗯
yeah,he's here.
是的，他在这儿
Hold on.
等等
how doesshe know you're here?
她怎么知道你在这里？
I don't know.
我不知道
hi. Ahem.
嗨
Yeah,I just came by to help julie with her civics homework.
是的，我就是过来 辅导一下julie功课
Uh-huh.
是的
Okay,I'll take care of it. What kind of juice do you want?
好 我会处理的 你想要什么果汁？
Right. Bye,bye.
好的 再见
Are you getting juicefor her?
你要给她带果汁？
Yeah,just one carton.
是的，就一箱
You rippedthe woman's heart out.
你伤透了这个女人的心
Why would she want juicefrom you?
为什么她会要你带果汁？
Okay. now don't freak out,
Okay，现在不要抓狂
but this breakup issort of a work in progress.
但是这个分手的事情 是一个进行中的事情
She doesn't know?
她不知道？
Will you calm down?I can explain.
你冷静下来好吗？我可以解释的
So if edie doesn't know, then that means that you just cheatedon her...
那如果edie不知道 那你就是在背着她红杏出墙……
with me!
和我！
You made me the other woman!
你让我成为了第三者！
Please don't be angry.
请不要生气
I tried to break up with her,
我试过和她分手
but because I wasn't sureyou wanted me back,
但是因为我不肯定你会接受我回来
the words just wouldn't come out of my mouth.
我总是欲言又止
Now that I know that you want me and love me again,
现在我知道了你是要我，是爱着我的
it's a done deal.
这件事就肯定要做了
get out of my house, you miserable son of a bitch!
滚出我的房子，你这个可悲的狗杂种！
can't we talk about this?
我们就不能谈谈吗？
No,just get out!Get out!
不，滚出去！滚出去！
Susie,susie!
Susie，susie！
Our marriage was garbage!
我们的婚姻就是垃圾！
- Stupid,disgusting pile of garbage!
- 愚蠢的令人厌恶的一堆垃圾
No,no,don't say that.
不，不，别这么说
And I regret everything that came of it!
- 我后悔和你做过的每一件事！
Don't do this right now.
不要马上就这么干
Ugh! Except you,honey.You're my rock.
除了你，甜心 你是我的骄傲
Ooh,out! Get out!
Ooh，出去！滚出去！
I...ugh!
我……！
I promise you I'm gonna break up with edie and make this right.
我保证会和edie分手 让事情回到正轨
I'll call you when it's done.
我会在完事后给你电话的
Don't bother!I won't pick up.
别麻烦了！我不领这个情
we've all done something in our lives we're ashamed of.
在生活中，我们都做过一些 我们为之羞愧的事情
Some of us have fallen for the wrong man.
我们中一些人爱上了错误的人
Some have let go of the right woman.
一些人放走了合适的女人
There are those who have humiliated their parents...
有使他们的父母丢脸的孩子……
and those who have failed their children.
有使他们的孩子失望的父母
Yes, we've all made mistakes that diminish us
是的，我们都犯过错误
and those we love.
使我们爱的人离我们而去
But there is redemption
但是仍然有挽回的机会
if we try to learn from those mistakes...
如果我们试着从这些错误中 汲取经验教训……
and grow. The Desperate Housewives Season 02  Episode 19
使自己成熟起来 绝望的主妇 第2季 第19集
The End-
=完=-